Here we go! It's a mess!
Continuing from the previous round, we have the Sensitive Championship.
In the second round, we're going to challenge you to a full-blown sensible game of "Quote Cutting"!
As the name implies, this is a quotation cutting.
As you all know...
This time, we'll continue.
Because it's a pull! Because it's a pull!
Next time
My true colors are showing.
LOL!
I could have sworn you just did that.
That's funny.
I'm like, "Oh, my God, I'm so excited." I'm like, "Oh, my God.
I said, "What kind of war?
Blindfold me.
This sword.
This stick.
You hold this urethane sword.
If you cut your opponent, you win.
We'll play it like a tournament.
One time.
Who do you want to fight?
I'll have to point them out to you.
Okay.
Okay.Seino.
Yuzu. Yuzu is better, right?
Yuzu is better.
Yuzu's too loud.
I know. Is that what you're saying?
That's why I can sense him.
Yuzu's not athletic.
That's got nothing to do with it.
You're not a bad athlete.
I know I'm not bad.
I'm just athletically inclined.
I'm not admitting it.
Because you're really not bad.
I really am.
I'm...
I'd like to beat him the best.
I mean, like a rival.
Because we're partners.
I want to cut him down to the bone.
I see.
What about you, Mayaka?
Aira is the center of the group.
I can tell.
By their aura.
It's true, I can feel her aura.I could certainly feel the aura of the
The center is what I
want to take it.
I want to win with this.
You did it, Modaka!
We won the Kiai Kirikiri.
It's like we're competing for the center.
Hanako...
Sensei was reinstated the other day.
Everyone got their teacher reinstated.
We're all in the same group.
I want to do it.
No one wants to do it.
You're so small.
I think Momoyaka is good at making people look small.
I'm sorry...
I don't have much of a shadow.
Shadows.
I'm good at making shadows thinner.
Come here.
This one's thinner.
I think I'm good at making the shadows thinner.
Not thin.
I don't like it.
Staff line one.Because the staff line one is overshadowed.
Not really. That's already the catchphrase.
Let's, Good Party! Let's break up!
Oh!
Let's break up!
Wow, that sucks.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That sucked.
That was the worst.
Okay, Yuzuka and Moeka and Aira...
We will fight in the first round.
Yes, sir.
So, for the first round, here are the two of you.
Ta-da!
Thank you very much.
Now, stick your "Eeyore" in the direction where you think Airahana is.
I don't know where it is.
I didn't put it in.
I put it here.
Let's go around.
Let's go.
One.
Two.
Three.3
1 bad
One back.
Okay, then.
No, hey.
You'd better watch those things.
All right, here we go.
Wait a minute.
Wait one time.
No, no, no.
It's over.
And it's over.
Try not to laugh.
Yes, so I guess we're back to square one.
Oh, Mr. Magu.
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
I'm going to go around five times.
Don't talk.Don't talk.
Then I'll stop.
I'll never laugh.
Then I'll turn it.
One.
Two.
Three.
Are you leaving?
Okay, I'm going to go get you a cover up.
Go ahead.
Four, five, OK.
I can't move the poacher at all.
All right, let's go!
Good night.
Oh, me? You hit my hair.
Oh, no?
How's that? It's...
We're sharing a loaf of bread. That was two people sharing a loaf of bread.
Maybe we'll get a second chance.
Third time.
Okay, so it was at the same time.
I'd like to go one more time.
Yes, sir.
Yes, thank you. Good luck.
I'll do my best.I'll do my best.
I'll do my best
I'll do my best.
I'll hold on.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay, let's do it.
Stop!
There you go.
Here we go.
All right, start!
Yeah!
So fast!
So, Ayanan wins!
Yeah!
I lost!
Okay, after the sound on the right.
And it shows up with a funny face.
Now next is Yuzuka's challenge.
Ta-da.Well then....
I'm sorry, Ichikawa-san, but these sandals,
Are they OK?
Are they not bad?
They are not good.
They'll definitely make noise.
It's not good.
Let's walk a little bit.
Let's walk a little.
Yuzu is the only sound.
It makes so much noise.
No, but this is it.
Well, it's a small island.
Oh, I see.
I see.
You'll win with the sensitive Kojima-san.
You'll win even with this.
I see.
Then I have high expectations for you.
It would be great if you win with this.
I remember you.
Then, let's give it a try.
Then, I'd like to try five times.
Five times.
Seino.Se.
Five.
I don't get it at all anymore.
I'm so surprised.
I'm sorry.
Then, please take five steps.
Ready.
One, two, three, four, five.
Okay.
I'll go.
Go ahead!
Oh!
This is how it's done.
It's so interesting.
That was a pretty good match.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Oh, man!
Not at all!Not at all.
I'm scared! We did the same thing to ourselves.
Hey.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Oh!
Well...
You hit it.
It's settled.
Winner, someday.
Winner.
You can take it.
I won with sandals, too.
But
Might not look good on your face
Screen out. Screen out.
It was a lie.
I lost.
Lie.
I'd like to play the "Billi Deciding Game.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stop.
All right, all right.All right!
Let's do it!
You two are so cool!
That's what I'm talking about in the finals.
You're on a different level.